ILGWU. National War Labor Board case files, 5780/085
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- M. Kofsky and Company. NWLB Case no.480, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Kragston (Kessler and Schwartz). NWLB Case no.386, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Kreinick Modes. NWLB Case no.304, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- L and M Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.358, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- L and M Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.401, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  See also NWLB Case no.358
- Ladies' Apparel Retailer's Guild. NWLB Case no.47, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Edith Lances. NWLB Case no.484, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Lane-Bryant, Inc. NWLB Case no.141, NWLB Case no.240, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Lastlong Underwear. NWLB Case no.237, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Lastlong Underwear. NWLB Case no.445, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  See also NWLB Case no.237
- LaTerre Garment Company. NWLB Case no.159, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 21a)
- B. M. Laursitsen and Company. NWLB Case no.246-D, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 21b)
- Leask Manufacturing Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.59, 1941-1945 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Leask Manufacturing Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.260, 1941-1945 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  See also NWLB Case no.59
- Leask Manufacturing Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.472, 1941-1945 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  See also NWLB Case no.59 and NWLB Case no.260
- Lederer Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.29, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Ledman Dress Company. NWLB Case no.360, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Lehigh Sportswear. NWLB Case no.88, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Lehigh Sportswear. NWLB Case no.435, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  See also NWLB Case no.88
- Ledie Dress Company. NWLB Case no.64, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Levy and Sachs. NWLB Case no.122, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Liberty Frocks. NWLB Case no.163, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Lilliput. NWLB Case no.363, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Lilliput. NWLB Case no.405, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 32a)
  See also NWLB Case no.363
- Linder Brothers. NWLB Case no.352, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Linder Brothers. NWLB Case no.61, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 33a)
- Linder Brothers. NWLB Case no.413, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  See also NWLB Case no.352
- Lion Brothers. NWLB Case no.181, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- B. J. Loeb Company. NWLB Case no.84, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- London Dress. NWLB Case no.309, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Lord and Taylor. NWLB Case no.366, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Lounging Robe. NWLB Case no.77, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Love Baby Frocks, Inc. NWLB Case no.246-E, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 39a)
- Lowenbaum Company. NWLB Case no.37, 1941-1943 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Lowenbaum II (Vacation). NWLB Case no.155, 1941-1943 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Lubell Contractors. NWLB Case no.281, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Edith Lutyens. NWLB Case no.489 (n.d.) (Box 4, Folder 43)
- M and S Robes. NWLB Case no.320, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Made Well. NWLB Case no.410, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Mademoiselle Swiss. NWLB Case no.432, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Maidenform Brassiere Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.227, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Maidenform Brassiere Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.325, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  See also NWLB Case no.227
- Maidenform Brassiere Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.429, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  See also NWLB Case no.227 and NWLB Case no.325
- Malone Knitting Company. NWLB Case no.101, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Manhattan Scalloping and Embroidery Works. NWLB Case no.196, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Mansbrooke Rainwear Company. NWLB Case no.36, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Louis Marcus Corporation. NWLB Case no.182, 1937-1942 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Marmon Sportswear. NWLB Case no.336, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Marmon Sportswear. NWLB Case no.448, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  See also NWLB Case no.336
- Marvel Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.173, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Marvel Underwear and Pajama Company. NWLB Case no.212, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Marvel Underwear and Pajama Company. NWLB Case no.323, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  See also NWLB Case no.212
- Marvel Underwear and Pajama Company. NWLB Case no.332, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Maxine Coat Company. NWLB Case no.437, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Maybelle Sportswear. NWLB Case no.8, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Mayflower Dress Company. NWLB Case no.15, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Mayflower Dress Company. NWLB Case no.364, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Mayflower Dress Company. NWLB Case no.375, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  See also NWLB Case no.364
- Mayflower Dress Company. NWLB Case no.431, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  See also NWLB Case no.15, NWLB Case no.364, NWLB Case no.375
- Mayflower Dress Company. NWLB Case no.441, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  See also NWLB Case no.15, NWLB Case no.364, NWLB Case no.375, NWLB Case no.431
- McCall Company. NWLB Case no.421, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- McCreery. NWLB Case no.368, 1939-1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- McKettrick Williams, Inc. NWLB Case no.160, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- McKettrick Williams, Inc. NWLB Case no.456, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- McKettrick Williams, Inc. NWLB Case no.197, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Merit Garment. NWLB Case no.425, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Mid-American Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.193, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Mijan, Inc. NWLB Case no.303, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Milady Brassiere. NWLB Case no.285, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- J and S Milberg. NWLB Case no.211, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Milgrim and Brothers, Inc. NWLB Case no.329, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Milgrim and Brothers, Inc. NWLB Case no.376, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  See also NWLB Case no.210 and NWLB Case no.377
- Milgrim and Brothers, Inc. NWLB Case no.471, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  See also NWLB Case no.210 and NWLB Case no.376
- Miller Corset Company. NWLB Case no.79, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Minersville Dress Company. NWLB Case no.272, 1941-1943 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Minneapolis Dress Company. NWLB Case no.146, 1941-1943 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Miss Angie. NWLB Case no.491 (n.d.) (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Missouri Garment. NWLB Case no.129, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Miss Swank. NWLB Case no.216, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Miss Swank. NWLB Case no.444, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  See also NWLB Case no.216
- Mitchell Garment. NWLB Case no.315, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Monmouth Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.422, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Mt. Vernon Garment. NWLB Case no.112, 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Movie Star Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.60, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- N and B Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.106, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  See also NWLB Case no.209
- N and B Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.209, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  See also NWLB Case no.106 and Kay Dunhill, NWLB Case no.208
- N and B Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.345, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  See also NWLB Case no.106 and NWLB Case no.209
- Nancy Belle, Inc. NWLB Case no.57, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Nassau Brassiere Company. NWLB Case no.483, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  See also NWLB Case no.102
- Nassau Brassiere Company. NWLB Case no.102, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- National Die and Button Mould. NWLB Case no.297, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- N.W.L.B. Forms. NWLB Case no.1, 1941-1945 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- N.W.L.B. Forms. NWLB Case no.10, 1941-1945 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- N.W.L.B. Forms. NWLB Case no.246, 1941-1945 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- N.W.L.B. Forms - Cotton Garment Attachments., 1941-1945 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- N.W.L.B. Forms - I.L.G.W.U. Wage Stabilization Forms No Longer Used., 1941-1945 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- N.W.L.B. Forms - No Longer Used. [folder 1 of 2], 1941-1945 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- N.W.L.B. Forms - No Longer Used. [folder 2 of 2], 1941-1945 (Box 5, Folder 37a)
- Newbridge Dress. NWLB Case no.80 1/2, 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- New England MacKintosh Company. NWLB Case no.38, 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- New Haven Waist and Dress. NWLB Case no.365, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- New Jersey Garment Company., 1942-1945 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- New Jersey Garment Company. NWLB Case no.274, 1942-1945 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- New Jersey Ladies Coat Company. NWLB Case no.411, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors. NWLB Case no.222, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- New York Belt Association (Ladies). NWLB Case no.206, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- New York Belt Association (Mens). NWLB Case no.205, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- New York Belt Association (Syndicate). NWLB Case no.10, 1941-1943 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- New York Blouse. NWLB Case no.121, 1941-1946 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- New York Blouse. NWLB Case no.501, 1941-1946 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  See also NWLB Case no.121
- New York Bonnaz Embroidery. NWLB Case no.157, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  See also NWLB Case no.85
- New York Children's Dress. NWLB Case no.233, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- New York Cloak Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.42, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- New York Cloak and Suit Industry. NWLB Case no.224, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- New York Corday Embroidery. NWLB Case no.25, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- New York Corset Industry. NWLB Case no.8, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- New York Cotton Apparel and Robe Association (Local 91). NWLB Case no. 447, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  See also NWLB Case no.58
- New York Cotton Apparel and Robe Association (Local 91). NWLB Case no. 58, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- New York Covered Button. NWLB Case no.113, 1941-1944 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- New York Covered Button. II - NWLB Case no.174, 1941-1944 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  See also NWLB Case no.113
- New York Covered Button. NWLB Case no.343, 1941-1944 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  See also NWLB Case no.113 and NWLB Case no.174
- New York Dress, re: Cutters. NWLB Case no.287, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- New York Embroidery Industry. NWLB Case no.85, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- New York House Dress Association (Industrial Association of House Dress, Robe Uniform Manufacturers). NWLB Case no.241, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- New York Neckwear. NWLB Case no.242, 1942-1944 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  See also NWLB Case no.20
- New York Neckwear. NWLB Case no.20, 1942-1944 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- New York Neckwear (Independent). NWLB Case no.103, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- New York Plastic Products Manufacturers Association. NWLB Case no.379, 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  See also NWLB Case no.249
- New York Plastic Products Manufacturers Association. NWLB Case no.249, 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- New York Skirt. NWLB Case no.502, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- New York Snow Suit (Local 105)., 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- New York Snow Suit (Local 105)., 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- New York Truckers. NWLB Case no.278, 1939-1944 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- New York Tubular, Piping and Trimming, Inc. NWLB Case no.98, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- New York Undergarment Manufacturers. NWLB Case no.99, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- New York Underwear., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Nitecraft Corporation., 1942-1944 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Nite Kraft Corporation. NWLB Case no.201, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- North Star Coat Company. NWLB Case no.167, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- M. Notkin. NWLB Case no.175, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Novel Products Company. NWLB Case no.268, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Novel Products Company. NWLB Case no.298, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  See also NWLB Case no.268
- Olympic Cloak Sunset Coat., 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Original Brenner Brothers, Inc. NWLB Case no.35, 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Original Brenner Brothers, Inc. NWLB Case no.215, 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  See also NWLB Case no.35
- Oneita Knitting Mills. NWLB Case no.500, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  See also NWLB Case no.476
- Oneita Knitting Mills. NWLB Case no.476, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- P. V. Shirt and Empirical Coat Company. NWLB Case no.335, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- D. Pagliaro. NWLB Case no.381, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Paterson Cloak and Suit. NWLB Case no.460, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Patricia Undergarment., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Paul. NWLB Case no.45 (n.d.) (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Pennsylvania Dress Manufacturers Association. NWLB Case no.495, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Petronion Dress. NWLB Case no.397, 1944-1947 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Philadelphia Associations. NWLB Case no.34, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Philadelphia Knitwear. NWLB Case no.267, 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Pioneer Dress. NWLB Case no.351, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Pioneer Dress. NWLB Case no.378, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  See also NWLB Case no.351
- Pittston Dress. NWLB Case no.398, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Plaza Knitting Mills. NWLB Case no.82, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- B. Podell and Sons. NWLB Case no.234, 1942-1944 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- G. M. Poix. NWLB Case no.312, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Portnoy Garment. NWLB Case no.259, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Printz-Biederman. NWLB Case no.52, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Prosperity Blouse. NWLB Case no.270, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Prosperity Cloak Company. NWLB Case no.140, 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Prosperity Cloak Company. NWLB Case no.372, 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  See also NWLB Case no.124
- Prosperity Cloak Company. NWLB Case no.493, 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  See also NWLB Case no.124 and NWLB Case no.372
- Puritan Mills. NWLB Case no.327, 1942-1945 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Putnam Manufacturing Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.144, 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Putnam Manufacturing Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.409, 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  See also NWLB Case no.144
- Quality Blouse. NWLB Case no.294, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Quality Blouse. NWLB Case no.67, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Rabhor Robe Company. NWLB Case no.80, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Rainbow Dress Company. NWLB Case no.14, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  See also NWLB Case no.135
- Rainbow Dress Company. NWLB Case no.135, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Rayfran, Inc. NWLB Case no.388, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Rayon Corporation. NWLB Case no.219, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Reisner. NWLB Case no.71, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Rex Products Corporation. NWLB Case no.127, 1941-1943 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- J. Rogow and Son. NWLB Case no.123, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Romano Dress Company. NWLB Case no.456C, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Rose Dress Shop. NWLB Case no.346, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Rosenblatt - Three Rosenblatt Contractors. NWLB Case no.31, 1942-1944 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- J. S. Rosenburg. NWLB Case no.261, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Royal Garment Company. NWLB Case no.244, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Royal Miss. NWLB Case no.342, 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Royal Miss. NWLB Case no.414, 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  See also NWLB Case no.342
- Royal Undergarment Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.48, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Frank Rubinowitz. NWLB Case no.2, 1942-1944 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Frank Rubinowitz. NWLB Case no.202, 1942-1944 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  See also NWLB Case no.2
- Russeks Fifth Avenue, Inc. NWLB Case no.299, 1941-1945 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  See also NWLB Case no.110
- Russeks Fifth Avenue, Inc. NWLB Case no.110, 1941-1945 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Russeks Fifth Avenue, Inc. NWLB Case no.442, 1941-1945 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  See also NWLB Case no.110 and NWLB Case no.299
- Sally Blouse. NWLB Case no.295, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Sally Blouse. NWLB Case no.331, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Sani-Aqua Shower Curtains, Inc., 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Sawitz., 1942-1944 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Schiff and Miskin. NWLB Case no.446, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Schimel. NWLB Case no.402, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Secor Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.353, 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  See also NWLB Case no.177
- Secor Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.177, 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Seven Texas Firms. NWLB Case no.296, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  See also Carr, Esskay, Juvenile, Lauritsen, Love Baby, Texas Infants, Tex-son
- Seventh Avenue Sportswear. NWLB Case no.461, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- Shane Manufacturing. Company. NWLB Case no.119, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Sherman Manufacturing. NWLB Case no.478, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- J. Sherrow. NWLB Case no.27, 1939-1943 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- H. Shnek. NWLB Case no.436, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 66)
- Shuwall Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.10, 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Shuwall Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.265, 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  See also NWLB Case no.10
- Siegal Brothers. NWLB Case no.496, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 69)
- Simmons Sportswear Company. NWLB Case no.30, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 70)
- Franklin Simon. NWLB Case no.367, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Sipco, Inc. NWLB Case no.257, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Slenderform Dress. NWLB Case no.104, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Smolar Brothers, Inc. NWLB Case no.49, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Somerset Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.93, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Somerset Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.225, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Sporteens, Inc. NWLB Case no.89, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Stamford Pad Company. NWLB Case no.7, 1941-1943 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Stamford Waist. NWLB Case no.296, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Standard Dress Company. NWLB Case no.349, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Steelton Apparel Company. NWLB Case no.464, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Stein and Balin. NWLB Case no.300, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Sterling Corset Company. NWLB Case no.254, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Sterling Corset Company. NWLB Case no.467, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Sunbury Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.63, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Sunbury Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.271, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Superior Petticoat Company. NWLB Case no.73, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Superior Petticoat Company. NWLB Case no.288, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  See also NWLB Case no.73
- Sylvan Coat. NWLB Case no.86, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- I. Tannenbaum Sons. NWLB Case no.492, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- I. Tannenbaum Sons. NWLB Case no.439, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  See also NWLB Case no.165
- I. Tannenbaum Sons. NWLB Case no.165, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Texas Infants Dress Company. NWLB Case no.246-F, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 22a)
  See also NWLB Case Seven Texas Firms, no.246
- Tex-son Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.246-G, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 22b)
- Jay Thorpe, Inc. NWLB Case no.469, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Bergdorf and Goodman Company and H. Milgrim & Brothers, Inc. NWLB Case no.210, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Charles Toback and Son. NWLB Case no.390, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Trencher Belsky Inc. NWLB Case no.49, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Trillco Company. NWLB Case no.417, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Trojan Maid Company. NWLB Case no.273, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Tunkhannock Dress. NWLB Case no.458, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- United Cloak. NWLB Case no.387, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- U.S. Clothing Company. NWLB Case no.481, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Vanity Dress Company. NWLB Case no.394, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Virginia-Carolina Chemical. NWLB Case no.328, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Walnott Mills. NWLB Case no.503, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Washington Manufacturing Corporation. NWLB Case no.72, 1941-1946 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Washington Manufacturing Corporation. NWLB Case no.192, 1941-1946 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Washington Manufacturing Corporation. NWLB Case no.499, 1941-1946 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  See also NWLB Case no. 72 and NWLB Case no.192
- Wasserman Gowns. NWLB Case no.301, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Wear Rite. NWLB Case no.284, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Wear Rite. NWLB Case no.404, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  See also NWLB Case no.284
- Weathercraft Company. NWLB Case no.107, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Weinberger. NWLB Case no.83, 1942-1944 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Weinberger. NWLB Case no.277, 1942-1944 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  See also NWLB Case no.194
- Meyer Weiss. NWLB Case no.400, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Whitehall Dress Company. NWLB Case no.451, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- White Haven Dress Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.457, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Whittendon Garment Company. NWLB Case no.452, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Max Weison and Sons Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.138, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Max Weison and Sons Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.172, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Williamsburg Sportswear, Inc. NWLB Case no.44, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Wilmington Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.253, 1942-1945 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Wilmington Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.434, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  See also NWLB Case no.253
- Woodbury Mils. NWLB Case no.186, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Woodbury Mils. NWLB Case no.468, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Wyoming Frocks. NWLB Case no.450, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Yolanda Dress. NWLB Case no.90, 1941-1944 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Yolanda Dress. NWLB Case no.243, 1941-1944 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  See also NWLB Case no.90
- Z Dress. NWLB Case no.306, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- A.C.W.A. Cotton Garment Case. (1 of 2), 1943 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Exhibits; statements; advance releases
- A.C.W.A. Cotton Garment Case. (2 of 2), 1943 (Box 9, Folder 1a)
- Brackets - General, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Correspondence; approvable wage rates; use of brackets
- Brackets - Region II - New York Metropolitan Area. (1 of 3), 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Correspondence; approvable wage rates; advance releases
- Brackets - Region II - New York Metropolitan Area. (2 of 3), 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 3a)
- Brackets - Region II - New York Metropolitan Area. (3 of 3), 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 3b)
- Brackets - Region II - New York Excluding Metropolitan Area, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Approvable wage rates; advance releases
- Brackets - Region VII - Kansas City, 1943-1945 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Wage bracket determinations; correspondence; stabilized rates and rate earnings
- Brackets - Region VIII - Dallas, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Correspondence; use of brackets
- Case Analysis, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Wage stabilization cases; case lists
- Cotton Garment Directive, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Advance releases
- Duplicates. (1 of 3), 1941-1945 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Advance releases; appendices
- Duplicates. (2 of 3), 1941-1945 (Box 9, Folder 9a)
- Duplicates. (3 of 3), 1941-1945 (Box 9, Folder 9b)
- General Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- General Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- General Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Going Rates, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  Sound and test going rate brackets
- Cloaks Joint Board, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Correspondence; application to Treasury Department Salary Stabilization Unit for approval of several salary adjustments
- International - ILGWU, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  Application for approval of a voluntary wage or salary rate adjustment
- Local 10, 1941-1943 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Local 22, 1941-1943 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Local 40, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Local 48, 1941-1943 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Local 60, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Local 62, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Local 66, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Local 82, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Local 89, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Local 91, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Memoranda Submitted to War Labor Board, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Local Going Rates & Wage Stabilization I Women's Apparel Industry
- War Labor Board Precedents and Procedures. (1 of 3), 1941-1945 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Manual from Analysis of Wage Material; Wage Rates for Apparel Trades; Holiday Retroactive Pay; Application of Going Wage Brackets to Incentive Payment Plans; Wage Stabilization Approvable Wage Rates; Wage & Salary Schedules; Release Interpretations; Guaranteed Employment and Annual Wage Plans; Intra-Plant Wage Relationships; Procedures; Routines